Ernest L. Hartmann Papers MS211
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Digital files, 1993 -- 2007; MS211.010; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - 9/14/93 Copy of BQ Data - Bamada "RC 522" Ss 01-517 to 01-603, 1993-09-14; MS211-003
    Original is a floppy disk found in folder "New Ss 1-517 to 1-603" of box MS211.005.068, Series 5: Research and data. The folder contains a letter that gives some context for the data. The disk contains a single file, of no recognizable file type, called Boundary.1.
  - BQ small SPSS programs from BC vax, 2000; MS211-004
    Original is a floppy disk found in folder "BQ-BC data-2000." It was found in an envelope, the first of two disks wrapped in a letter, which remains in the folder, from Rani E. Dalgin of Boston College. The other disk is MS211-005. This disk contains many different file extensions including .SPPS, .OLD, and .LIS data files. From MS211.005.063 in Series 5: Research data and materials.
  - BQ raw data files from BC vax, 2000; MS211-005
    Original is a floppy disk found in folder "BQ-BC data-2000." It was found in an envelope, the second of two disks wrapped in a letter, which remains in the folder, from Rani E. Dalgin of Boston College. The other disk is MS211-004. This disk contains .DAT files. From MS211.005.063 in Series 5: Research data and materials.
  - Boundary Questionnaire data Hartman, 2001-03-01; MS211-006
    CD labeled "Hartman." Computer reads disk as "010301-1232." Contains 24 files, mostly .sas and .SPS files readable by SPSS and SAS. Files are Boundary Questionnaire data. CD contains a Readme.doc created by the original researcher which explains the context of the files and how to open them. Found in folder "BQ BC-BQ All Data Disc (CD)" in box MS211.008.078, Series 8: Unsorted boxes.
- Websites, 2014; MS211.000116; 2 Web sites
  This series is open for research.
  A collection of 2 websites crawled by DCA to document the presence of Ernest Hartmann on the web. The websites in this series were crawled on a one-time basis.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Archived websites can be viewed online using the Internet Archive's Wayback Machine.
  - Ernest Hartmann M.D.- Dreaming Boundaries Nightmares, 2014; MS211.000117; 1 Web sites
  - Ernest Hartmann: Selected Papers to 2013, 2014; MS211.000118; 1 Web sites